Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there?
Hold on for me!
On this long journey that
we've only barely begun!
Friendship, love, courage,
and a little bit of fun!
These are the things!
That even as the years go by!
Will not ever vanish from our minds!
We are all pieces of
a single planet Earth!
Little by little we can
find each other's worth!
And as we see what sort of
form we're meant to take!
All of us know the wind will
always keep on blowing away!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Look through that wind to dry!
All the tears as you're bleeding!
The things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
All the tears you shed will help
you to become so much stronger!
All the tears you shed
will help you to remember!
Everything, everything, everything!
Now and forever!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, yay!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you
as you finish what you've begun!
Let's do that wind to dry all the tears as
you're plating the
things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure,
found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
And this washed up
former warlord over here!
Yeah, I mean you, Crocodile!
I heard you got your ass handed to you!
But I didn't know Straw Hat
Luffy was the one to do it!
Funny thing is!
I was trying to take Crocodile's
place as a warlord at the time!
So killing you was about the
best way I could think of!
to show the government I
was worthy of the position.
Whitebeard's days are
numbered and you know it.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates. First,
I'm headed off to Water
7 to kill Straw Hat
Luffy as a special gift
to the world government.
Wouldn't hurt to have
you along for the fun.
You know him?
Of course I know him, you sack of crap.
I'm not gonna let you
kill my little brother.
And yet here you are
Fate decided to save you instead
Ace had been chasing after
me to get revenge for my so
-called crime on Whitener's
ship And I had been chasing
you Of course I couldn't team
up with him to kill you But
it all worked out Because we
both got the fight we wanted
Henry ate it If he'd let
us get away He'd not only
disgrace Whitebeard's name
But he'd also be turning his
back on his brother And
leaving you to die There is no
such thing as coincidence
When it comes to fate Truly
Yeah, and you god lucky kiddo
You weren't fated to die
Our captain achieved his goal
of becoming a warlord Thanks
to your brother So you're
thoroughly useless to us now
Wee ha ha
Ole's put up a brave fight And
it just didn't work out for him
Better make sure you pay your
humble respects At his grave strike
He went and took your place
for you Because if it weren't
for your brother You'd be
dead and he'd be walking free
That's the truth.
Try to kill me now! Huh?
Captain!
I'm not gonna let my brother die!
Come, come!
Change!
The Black Vortex!
Straw Boy!
Lord, I thought it was made of rubber.
You don't even realize what
the hell I just did, do you?
That's how I broke your
miserable brother! Now,
just like him, your devil-proof powers are
about as useless as money to a dickman!
So what?
You think that matters?
Luffy, that's enough. Calm yourself.
Let go, David.
Get out of my way.
Take one. Open.
Let go of me.
Stop and listen to me.
What is your objective here?
Is fighting going to
help you accomplish it?
As long as I've known him,
Teach has always been a mystery.
Even when he was a nobody
on Whitebeard's crew.
I don't know where the
Cretan got his powers from,
but not even your invincible
brother was strong
enough to overcome that
terrifying darkness.
It's pointless for you to waste
your time and energy fighting him,
and it sure as hell's not
going to do Ace any good.
You can't save your brother
if you get yourself killed.
You're stronger than I
expected, Straw Hack.
You got more Haki than you did last time.
Your name is Blackbeard. You said.
Then you're the nameless pirate
I've heard so much about the one
who was part of Whitebeard's crew
until he took my place as warlord.
But this is rather odd.
Surely they summoned you to Navy
headquarters for the execution.
So why are you here?
It's clear enough how much you
coveted the title of warlord.
So why would you risk losing
it to come to this dump?
It's all a part of my grand scheme.
If you're that interested, I
suppose I can lay it out for you.
Is that what you want, Mr. Crocodile?
No. I'm fine.
To be honest, I couldn't care less.
Got a heart made of ice.
This one does.
Whoa, what the hell?
What's happening now?
Warden Magellan is here!
There goes the party.
Hey, Straw Boy, you gotta get out of here!
You can't take the risk of
Magellan poisoning you again!
You were lucky the first time around,
but you won't survive another one!
He's gonna be here any second!
Run!
Come on, guys! Let's go!
Warden Magellan's here!
We're saved.
We're finally saved.
Magellan.
So I finally get to meet the monster.
Head up the stairs!
The mazooka troops have cleared out!
There's nothing in our way now!
Hey, Straw Hat!
Hurry up and hit those stairs!
Get to level three, okay?
We appreciate you scattering
their defense on the staircase.
I must at least give you your due.
On that one you helped us out too.
You know this would have been
a hell of a lot harder without?
about the panic you caused!
Clear!
We've got a straight shot to level three!
Freedom, here we come!
Hurry, I'll take another
frickin' demon guard!
It's Minotaurus this time!
What? Minotaurus?
I could have swore that we already beat him
into a massive mound of hamburger patty!
Doesn't really matter if you did.
Each one of them has awakened
Zoan-type Devil Fruit powers.
They were already strong.
Now they're practically invulnerable.
What?
Are you serious?
Those monsters ain't a Devil Fruit!
We need to hurry this up.
Who knows how little time we've
got before the other three recover.
Also, if you're gonna piss your
pants, don't waste it on them.
Because we've already got the
boss of hell hot on our tail.
Warden Magellan, sir.
I just received a report that Blackbeard
has already infiltrated this floor.
And he's at the staircase
to level three as we speak.
I put that lunatic sheet of you
in charge of holding them back.
Was he defeated?
This is the monitoring room. What now?
We've got a problem, sir.
We've lost the visual feed
in all of our monitors.
Someone broke the vision
receiver transponder snail.
And if that wasn't already bad enough,
all communication channels
to Navy HQ have been cut off.
So we can't even contact...
What?
What's going on here?
Hey! Keep talking! What's happening?
Do you know who's behind the blackout?
Can't have you blowing my cover.
I want this to be a
surprise for the boss man.
We've lost communication
with communications!
Get someone up there to
find out what's going on!
Yes, sir!
It just keeps getting worse.
The only way Blackbeard could
have made it to this floor?
Is if he overcame the toxic blockades.
I placed over the exits on level two.
And that would make level two defenseless.
None of our plans are working.
We were careless enough to
let a single rat stay here.
And now we're up to our necks in vermin.
Buggy! Mr. Three! Buggy! Mr. Three!
Make way for genius!
We made it, guys!
We fought by killing, here we are!
Level one!
We're going to get to feel the sun on
our skin, and who do we have to thank?
Our brave and brilliant
savior, Captain Byron!
I'm saving it!
I'll find a way!
I ain't going to stop you, kid.
You give it your best.
Nothing's impossible in this world, after
all, but I've already told you that.
Remember Sky Island?
The era when pirates' dream of
treasure will come to an end?
Yeah, right!
The dreams of pirates will never end!
Am I right?
And just like Sky Island, the
One Piece is really out there.
I can't wait for you to see
what we've got in store.
Trust me, you're gonna be impressed!
In a few hours,
we're gonna put on a show so explosive
that'll shake the whole damn world.
Ignore him, Luffy, come on!
Keep moving boys straight to level three.
Can you please get me down from here?
Stop staring you creeps!
Help me calm down!
Tell me what happened to you, Sadie?
That damn Yvonne cough!
Beat me and tied me up!
Just get me down!
Do you know how humiliating it
is to do this to a dominatrix?
Help her, man.
I don't have time to deal with this.
Yes, sir!
Right away!
I've got a funny feeling you're Magellan.
And I'm guessing you're Blackbeard.
Hit the nail right on
the head, pal. Hydra!
I'm too busy trying to run this prison to
even bother asking what you're doing here.
Oh, what is this stuff?
Dammit, it's gotta be some kind of poison!
Get back here!
Panyable.
I'm impressed with how long you held out.
I'll take the rest from here
Is the Vice Warden all right, sir?
Oh, no, he looks terrible.
Quit gawking and help him out!
Yes, sir!
Vice Warden, just hang in there, okay?
Can you hear me, sir?
You can't die, Hannibal?
You're the only one who
can possibly take my place.
Straw Hat, how the hell could you
possibly survive after I poisoned you?
There's no doubt that he's the
one who caused all this mayhem.
The next chance I get, nothing
will stop me from taking his life.
You hear that Magellan's coming that
came from the foot of the stairs?
We're all dead who catches
up to us the poison guy!
I promise you this, Straw Hat.
You will never escape this prison.
Keep running, trust me, you
don't want to look back!
You can't escape from me.
Let's hurry.
That was the last group.
Everyone else who was behind
them is no longer standing.
They didn't make it.
Inazuma?
Ready to go!
Great scissors.
Inazuma?
Wait.
Why'd you just cut the staircase
Eva hasn't come up yet?
All you need to worry about
is getting out of here
I'll do that you said.
This is suicide.
What are you hoping to accomplish?
Curious, are we?
If you can't figure it out,
you must be terribly slow.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What I meant to say.
Is that your stupid.
Death.
Wing.
Even if
you do buy
yourself some time,
Straw Hat and his little friend still
have no means of escape by some time.
Goodness, how cheeky.
Already convinced you
can beat me, are you?
Kamabaka style.
New Kamakenpo.
Feast your eyes on this Drop boy.
Move it, boys.
Freedom's waiting for you.
Thanks, Captain Boogie.
Yes, I can't believe it.
Have a weapon and do your
part. There you go. Thanks.
Take this.
Let's go!
To the top!
After a stroke of luck allowed
them to escape from level two,
which had been blocked
by Magellan's poison?
Captain Buggy, Mr.
Three, and the others are
closing in on the main entrance.
They are now on level one.
Led by Luffy,
the mob of newcomers
and the prisoners they
freed continue their
ascent through Impel Down.
Running through level four and three,
They've now made their way to
level two, the Wild Beast Hell,
where they've found
surprisingly little resistance.
Meanwhile,
Ivankov has put a temporary
halt to Warden Magellan's
poisonous pursuit by doing
battle with him on level three.
My spine.
It hurts so much.
Damn you, Ivankov.
Unforgivable.
Get up!
After them!
Earn your feet, or I'm going to
slap them beating out of you!
Despite their repeated defeats.
Sadie has used a unique
brand of motivation!
To coax the demon guards into another
battle on level one jail manager Shit
you who is now Running wild cut all
lines of communication with the outside
world so that no one could discover
This situation within the prison and so
the unprecedented events happen one after
another Literally behind closed doors.
Fortunately for us impel town
is surrounded by prison ships?
and Navy ships.
If we could somehow manage
to steal one of them,
we could use a ticket to Marineford?
before Ace's execution.
Works for me.
Hold on, Ace.
We're coming for you.
Only four hours remain!
Until Ace's public execution?
at Navy headquarters.
Hmm? Hmm. Hmm.
It's up!
Long on the next.
Shemaze.
Hey, something's weird.
Where's the poison guy?
He was right behind him.
I'm sure it's no coincidence that Eva
and Inazuma stopped in the lower level.
What?
They stayed behind to fight
their poison guy by themselves?
Ralphs, we need to help them.
Let's go back.
Are you pulling my tail?
They don't call him a
miracle worker for nothing.
If he thinks he can handle the big
boss, then be grateful and keep moving.
Ralphs and Ralphs, I go.
There's something fishy going on.
We're getting through here way too easy.
Indeed.
I was thinking the same thing.
Also, I don't see any
prisoners in the cells.
And all of the doors are wide open.
Someone must have come through
and released them, but why?
Oh my mate!
I can feel it melting away!
Oh, the pain, the agony,
oh, my beautiful face, you monster,
ah, I was going to melt, melt,
melt, or not.
Ha, my makeup protected me.
Ha, ha, ha, yee-haw!
Ha, ha, ha, death, wink, wink, wink.
Death!
Death! Death!
Venom Blowfish!
Oh, no!
Why in a time like this?
My boot laces!
Or maybe not because these beauties are
laceless there's no
laces you got me there?
There's nothing to gain by
stalling for time think so?
Oh but I'm having so much fun doing it!
Fine then have it your way!
You want to end this?
How about right now?
New Kama Kenpo 44.
Aesthetic Technique.
Hair Removal Fist.
He's still alive.
Let him roll.
Eva.
Oh no!
Now cave out!
You're trying to stall me too!
The four demon guards
are the ones! We screwed!
It's all over!
Come back to yourselves!
You can't fight them!
The whole freaking up
thing is canceled, okay?
Come on, let's pull it together!
You bastard!
What are you trying to...
Holy crap!
Oh, it's been a while, Mr. Three.
I see you're a whimpering
imbecile, just like before.
Who in their right mind would
release this pain in the butt?
C-Captain Buggy!
Look!
Those guys knocked out
all four demon guards!
Wado?
And that's the war on team day!
There you are!
God, I'm glad you guys are okay!
He is too, Bugs!
Oh, it just breaks my heart!
Captain Buggy, look!
There are a bunch of released
prisoners and perverts
that are coming up one after
another from level two!
Perverts do?
What the hell?
Who are you calling perverts?
This is what you two goons get
for walking out on us back there!
Thanks a lot!
What are you doing, Captain Buggy?
This is bad.
Those prisoners are from level four,
and they made it all the way up here!
How'd they get away from
Warden Magellan?! Damn it!
Two riots happened at the
same time under our watch!
Where's the warden now?
Hydra!
Magellan's here too?!
What is happening on this floor?! Oh crap!
Something bad happened
to even the crab guy!
Don't beat up, straw boy!
Running is the only option
we've got with Magellan!
Let go of me now!
I'm not gonna run, I'm gonna kick his ass!
Yes, sir, but are you sure?
I understand, but that's
really what you want? Yes.
Set up everything just as I've explained.
And do it as quickly as possible.
Yes, sir.
Damn it.
So that's what he's got up his sleeve.
Damn it!
Just forget it!
You barely laid a finger on him last
time, and you're lucky he didn't kill you!
Yeah, but I'm still alive, aren't I?
Miracles don't happen again and again.
That's why they're miracles
in the first place.
Quit horse-playing, you two,
and get to the upper level.
Now, Luffy, we have to get to
the main entrance, post-haste.
Things aren't looking good for us.
We were paying too much
attention to Magellan.
Hydra.
Heads up, you guys!
Candle, whoa!
Nice! Yeah!
He stopped telling his
hydra right in his tracks!
Your naivety still sickens me, so
don't get the wrong idea, all right?
I may have saved your life,
but that doesn't mean I want to
be friends or any of that mess.
Honestly, I'm just sick of owing
you a damn favor, that's all!
I like you even more now, brother three!
Devil Fruit powers, huh?
Is that wax?
Yep, precisely.
I ate the wax wax fruit and
gained these handy powers.
This wall might as well be made of iron.
I can promise you this.
Your venom is not
getting through it. Hmph.
Glad that pile of garbage was
good for something after all.
Just goes to show that every power
has a use somewhere or another. Go!
Get out of here, dammit!
I don't plan on keeping this up forever.
Thanks, man.
Meddlesome twit.
What are you standing around for?
This won't hold much longer.
All right, I'll lead
the charge out of here.
You heard him, let's go.
That is super handy.
Outside the burning hill, at least.
Now go, and I will be right behind you.
Get a head start and
clear the path for us.
Now, Luffy.
I'm getting tired of saying it.
Wait, didn't you tell me this would
only work if you stole a Navy ship?
That's right.
Then why don't you go with everyone else?
I want to stay behind
and try to stop this guy.
We're not going to have much chance
of stealing it with him chasing us.
That may be the case, but...
Don't you worry, I got a plan.
And you're confident in this?
Yeah, leave it to me.
All right, but don't go
and push yourself too hard.
Okay three let's get this fight going.
No hell no i don't want
to fight that monster.
I was just trying to buy us some time so
we can run away brother
three we aren't that
strong but we're here to help you you guys
got the wrong idea that's not what i want.
Face forward dammit this is not
the time to lose your focus.
I'm sorry but my eyes keep
filling up. with tears.
Thanks, man.
You made me into an ass-kicking machine.
Just shut up and start fighting!
Here it comes.
Hydra!
Three!
Right, I'm on it!
And the wall!
Keep trying, but you're
not getting through!
Goal, Goal, Champion, Rifle!
Awesome, I can touch him!
These cannons are loaded and good to go!
And we've got candle shields!
Take that!
We got the bastard!
We can do this!
We beat all the tough guys, that
means we can finally relax a bit!
You're letting your guard down.
Don't act like such an amateur. What?
Going by my last count, there are at
least 10 Navy ships waiting out there.
And each one has 800 marines on board.
I don't know their configuration,
but stealing one Navy ship
means that we're still
gonna have to contend with
the rest of the fleet.
Does that sound relaxing to you?
Yeah, you've got a point there.
And that's not the only problem we've got.
There are no more guards
to get in our way.
All that's left now is the front door.
All right.
Ready your weapons, everyone.
It's time to open this door.
Get ready.
And push.
I've finally got to get
to go home. Shut up.
We're not done yet, so don't jinx it.
There's one last giant hurdle
waiting for us out there.
A whole Navy fleet, so
we got a ways to go.
It's sunlight.
I can chase the freedom.
Get ready for the fight of your lives.
I don't care how many thousands
of Marines are waiting for us.
We're going to push right
through it, out to the sea!
It's now or never!
Let's go, boys!
Follow me to freedom!
What the hell?
Is this some kind of sick joke?
There's not a single-lady ship in sight!
But weren't we gonna steal one
of their ships to get away?
There's no guards, not even one Marine!
We're just as trapped as we always were!
It's not fair, what do we do?
The only option left is
to just wait here and
hope that Magellan kills
us mercifully and quickly.
Damn it!
This can't be happening!
They got us.
Gotta give them credit for not being
as stupid as I thought they were.
The water around here is
filled with giant sea kings.
As the saying goes, the Calm Belt is the
greatest barrier protecting Impel Down.
We clawed our way out
of the depths of hell
with our merry fingernails
just for this! Damn it!
Now we're gonna get dragged right
back into the flames and be tortured!
We don't have time to sit here moping!
Yes, the Navy's gone, but they only
cleared out because Magellan told them to.
And they're not far!
Look, and you can see the shadows
of their sails on the fog!
He's right!
But they're still too far off!
There's no way we've got
a chance of catching them!
It's never too late!
You've got me here, right?
So stand back and let me handle this.
Holy crap.
How freaking strong is he?
You want to keep moving?
Hop on.
Now, let's do this.
You ready?
Here we go.
He's swimming like a shark
with that thing when he's back!
Now that's the true captain
of the Fishman Pirates!
Oh man, this is gonna be crazy!
I can't wait to see how
the Warlord's gonna fight!
Not to mention our savior
Captain Buggy right beside him!
I can't help but feel
a little hopeful here!
How stupid are they?
It's a hell of a lot safer
to stick with a warlord
than stay behind and try to
face Magellan on your own,
idiots!
They're shooting!
Seems like they smarted us.
He dodged it!
He's too fast!
That's not just a fish man, that's
the first son of the sea, Jinbei!
All forces, open fire!
As long as we can sing Jinbei,
the rest of them are finished.
Here they are!
An entire fleet of ships!
I'm gonna launch you guys on the
deck, so hold on tight now! Huh?
Wait, you're what?
You maybe wanna run that plan
past us one more time, fish face?
What the...
the bastard's gone!
What the hell's going on?
I see.
He left us here his bait
and scram off on his own!
Traitor, traitor, traitor, traitor,
Why the hell did you come with us?
Jinbae!
How could you leave us like this?
We're sending cops out here.
Fishman Jiu-Jitsu!
Warheart!
It's coming straight forward!
Ocean current, shoulder throw!
We're flying!
What's with that water column?
It's moving like it's alive!
Do you have any idea what's causing it?
Not the foggiest, but I
can see people on the tip.
One of them's crocodile!
They're going to try to hijack the ship.
Stop them!
Attack them with everything you've got!
They've got Devil Fruit powers!
Just throw them in the water!